[bright music]
[明亮的音乐]
♪ ♪
[bubbling]
[冒泡]
- Snark Chat with Bubble Bass.
- Snark 与 Bubble Bass 聊天。
- And we're back.
- 我们回来了。
My first guest had dinner
with me just last night.
我的第一位客人吃晚饭了
昨晚和我在一起。
He's a close personal friend
of mine.
他是一位亲密的私人朋友
我的。
Please welcome
the Krabby Patty.
欢迎
蟹肉饼。
Great to have you back
on the program.
很高兴你回来
节目上。
- Great to be here, BB.
- 很高兴来到这里，BB。
- Well, I'm sorry to say it,
but last night
- 好吧，我很遗憾地说，
但昨晚
you were not quite as delicious
as one would hope.
你没那么好吃
正如人们所希望的那样。
- Oh, don't worry.
- 哦，别担心。
I'm sure Mr. Krabs will give
you a refund.
我相信蟹老板会给
你退款。
[percussive sting]
[敲击式刺痛]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Bubble Bass, who are you
talking to down there?
- 泡泡巴斯，你是谁
在那里说话？
- Mother!
Please stop trying to undermine
- 母亲！
请停止试图破坏
my fantasy talk show!
我的奇幻脱口秀！
[thud]
Mmph.
[砰]
嗯。
- You march yourself upstairs
this instant!
- 你大步上楼
这一刻！
Take out the garbage,
dry the dishes,
把垃圾倒掉，
擦干餐具，
and walk the worm!
并行走蠕虫！
- Ooh, I don't feel like it!
- 哦，我不喜欢这样！
[thumping]
[怦]
Huh?
啊？
[squelch]
[静噪]
[shattering]
[破碎]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[chomping]
[咀嚼]
That tears it, Mother!
真是让人泪流满面啊，妈妈！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
I am moving out!
我要搬出去了！
- Moving?
Hah!
- 搬家？
哈！
You can't even
do your own laundry!
你甚至不能
自己洗衣服！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[fly buzzing]
[苍蝇嗡嗡声]
All I need to do is find
two able-bodied idiots.
我需要做的就是找到
两个身体健全的白痴。
But where am I to find
such stupidity
但我到哪里去找
如此愚蠢
on such short notice?
这么短的通知？
[laughter]
[笑声]
Hmm...
唔...
[crash]
[碰撞]
- Whoops.
- 哎呀。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Sorry, Bubble Bass.
对不起，泡泡巴斯。
- Why, you two
able-bodied idiots!
- 为什么，你们两个
有能力的白痴！
I--
[gasps]
我——
[喘气]
Ooh.
哦。
♪ ♪
Why, SpongeBob and Patrick,
my occasional friends.
为什么，海绵宝宝和帕特里克，
我偶尔的朋友。
How would you two
like to earn a free lunch?
你们两个会怎样
喜欢赚取免费午餐吗？
- Free lunch!
- 免费午餐！
- All righty, we're moving
all of my belongings
- 好吧，我们要搬家了
我所有的物品
out of my mother's basement
从我母亲的地下室出来
into my grandmother's basement
across town.
进入我祖母的地下室
穿过城镇。
Let's start with my lounge.
让我们从我的休息室开始吧。
- Okay, Patrick,
up with the loveseat.
- 好吧，帕特里克，
与双人沙发一起。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[snap]
[折断]
Ow!
噢！
My bad back!
我的背不好！
I guess you two will have to
move everything without me.
我想你们两个必须
移动一切，无需我。
So I'll meet you both
at this address.
所以我会见到你们俩
在这个地址。
- But don't you have to pack
your things
-但是你不需要打包吗
你的东西
before we can move 'em?
在我们移动它们之前？
- Ooh, ahh, I guess you'll
have to pack my stuff too.
- 哦，啊，我想你会的
还得收拾我的东西。
But remember what gastric
prizes await your mouths.
但请记住胃
奖品等待着您的嘴巴。
[boat horn blares]
[船喇叭声]
- Oh, Patrick...
- 哦，帕特里克...
[splashing]
[溅]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Okay, Patrick,
let's get p-p-p-packing!
- 好吧，帕特里克，
让我们打包吧！
[bright music]
[明亮的音乐]
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
- Oh...
- 哦...
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[hissing]
[嘶嘶声]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
[laughs]
[笑]
- Huh...
- 呃...
Hmm, mm.
嗯，嗯。
[chomp]
[咀嚼]
♪ ♪
[spitting]
[随地吐痰]
[coughs]
[咳嗽]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[splashing]
[溅]
[shattering]
[破碎]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
♪ ♪
[grunting, clanging]
[咕噜声，叮当声]
- [exclaims]
- [惊呼]
- [giggles]
- [咯咯笑]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- All right,
that's the last of it.
- 好吧，
这是最后一个。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
Whew, I hope we didn't
leave anything behind.
哇，我希望我们没有
留下任何东西。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
♪ ♪
[clanging]
[叮叮当当]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- [grunts, screams]
- [咕哝声，尖叫声]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Oh, pardon us, ma'am,
but could you walk around?
- 哦，请原谅我们，女士，
但你能四处走走吗？
- Walk around?
- 到处走走？
Hmph, I'm Lady Upturn
the 333rd,
哼，我是逆天大小姐
第333期，
and you want me to walk around?
你想让我到处走走吗？
[laughs]
I'm afraid you just have to
[笑]
恐怕你只需要
back it up.
备份它。
- Back it up?
- 备份吗？
[backup alarm blares]
[备用警报声]
Okay.
Back it up, Patrick.
好的。
支持一下，帕特里克。
- What'd you say?
- 你说什么？
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Oh, oh, oh!
- 哦，哦，哦！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[exclaiming]
[惊呼]
- Oh!
- 哦！
[spits]
[吐口水]
[exclaiming]
[惊呼]
[vrooming]
both: Huh?
两人：啊？
- Phew, hey, Patrick,
from now on,
- 唷，嘿，帕特里克，
从现在开始，
we gotta be more careful.
我们必须更加小心。
Huh?
Patrick.
啊？
帕特里克.
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
[exclaims]
[惊呼]
- Oh, focus, Patrick, focus!
- 哦，集中注意力，帕特里克，集中注意力！
- Okay.
- 好的。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- That's perfect.
- 那很完美。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[laughs]
[笑]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
♪ ♪
Hmm?
- [screams]
唔？
- [尖叫]
♪ ♪
[meowing]
[喵喵叫]
♪ ♪
- [mumbling]
I can walk!
- [咕哝]
我可以走路了！
Oh!
哦！
[laughing]
[笑]
- Ahh!
- 啊！
- Oh!
- 哦！
- [exclaiming]
- [惊呼]
[laughter]
[笑声]
both: Babies?
两人：宝贝们？
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[motor revs]
[电机转速]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[tires screech]
[轮胎尖叫声]
[babbling]
[胡说]
[thudding]
[重击]
- [grunts]
SpongeBob?
- [咕哝]
海绵宝宝？
Where are you?
你在哪里？
- [grunts]
I'm down here.
- [咕哝]
我在下面。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
- [giggles]
Shall we, SpongeBob?
- [咯咯笑]
我们可以吗，海绵宝宝？
- We shall, Patrick.
- 我们会的，帕特里克。
both: [humming]
两人：[哼哼]
[laughter]
[笑声]
both: Babies?
No!
两人：宝贝们？
不！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
[laughter]
[笑声]
both: Whoa!
两人：哇！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Hmm...hm?
- 嗯...嗯？
Hey, this is the address!
嘿嘿，这是地址！
We made it, Patrick!
我们成功了，帕特里克！
Nice aim, babies!
目标不错，宝贝们！
- Hooray!
- 万岁！
Now where's that free lunch?
现在免费的午餐在​​哪里？
[slurping]
[发出声音]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Focus!
重点！
Let's get all this stuff
inside the house,
让我们得到所有这些东西
房子里面，
then we can eat.
然后我们就可以吃饭了。
Hmm, hmm.
- Hmm, hmm.
嗯，嗯。
- 嗯，嗯。
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
- Oh, Bubble Bass,
special delivery.
- 哦，泡泡鲈鱼，
特别送货。
Hmm?
唔？
Hmm.
唔。
Okay, Patrick, push it!
好吧，帕特里克，推吧！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[thudding]
[重击]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
♪ ♪
[bang]
[砰]
And that's how you do it.
这就是你要做的。
- Uh-oh, Patrick.
- 呃哦，帕特里克。
Look what we did to
Bubble Bass' granny's house.
看看我们做了什么
泡泡巴斯奶奶的房子。
- This isn't Bubble Bass'
grandmother's house.
- 这不是泡泡巴斯
祖母的房子。
That is.
那是。
♪ ♪
This was my house!
- Well, that's a relief.
这是我的家！
- 嗯，这真是一种解脱。
For a minute there, I thought
we did something wrong.
有那么一分钟，我想
我们做错了什么。
- [spluttering]
- [溅水声]
[bang]
[砰]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
♪ ♪
- Don't look down, Patrick!
- 别往下看，帕特里克！
- I turned off my eyes.
- 我闭上了眼睛。
[wind gusting]
[阵风]
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇哇哇！
Oh!
[hiccups]
哦！
[打嗝]
- Uh-oh, Patrick,
I think I have the--
- 呃哦，帕特里克，
我想我有——
[hiccups]
[打嗝]
Hiccups.
- Hiccups?
打嗝。
- 打嗝？
I want some.
I'm so hungry!
我想要一些。
我好饿啊！
- [hiccups, exclaims]
- [打嗝，惊呼]
Here comes another one,
Patrick.
又一个来了，
帕特里克.
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Thanks, buddy.
We're almost there.
- 谢谢，伙计。
我们快到了。
Just a few more steps, and
we'll claim that free lunch.
只需再执行几步即可
我们会要求免费的午餐。
- Yeah--
[hiccups]
- 是的--
[打嗝]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Well, this is a dilly
of a pickle.
- 嗯，这是一个迪莉
一个泡菜。
[laughing]
[笑]
- Back it up!
- 支持一下！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Back it up!
支持一下！
[laughter]
[笑声]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
both: Oof.
Ta-da!
两人：噢。
哒哒！
Oof.
钱币。
- I hope you didn't damage
my goods.
- 我希望你没有损坏
我的货。
- Oh, your goods are all good,
Bubble Bass.
-哦，你的货都很好，
泡泡贝斯.
And we sure built up
an appetite
我们确实建立了
有食欲
for that free lunch.
为了那份免费的午餐。
[laughs]
[笑]
- [gulps]
- [吞咽]
[squeals]
[尖叫声]
- Oh, yes, about that.
- 哦，是的，关于那个。
I'm afraid I was waiting
for you so long
恐怕我一直在等待
为你这么久
that I ate them.
我吃了它们。
[chomping]
[咀嚼]
Mmm.
嗯。
[belches]
[打嗝]
- [whimpers]
- [呜咽]
- [inhales]
- [吸气]
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
If my friend SpongeBob
doesn't get his free lunch,
如果我的朋友海绵宝宝
没有得到免费的午餐，
things are gonna get crazy!
事情会变得疯狂！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
- That is the meanest thing
I ever saw, Bubble Bass.
- 这是最卑鄙的事
我见过，泡泡巴斯。
You, sir, have crossed
the line of aquatic decency.
先生你已经穿越了
水生礼仪线。
You may think you took
a couple of bottom feeders
你可能认为你拿了
几个底部喂食器
for a ride today,
but I have got a newsflash
今天去兜风，
但我有一个新闻快报
for you, slappy.
为了你，邋遢的。
These bottom feeders
wouldn't eat your free lunch
这些底部喂食器
不会吃你的免费午餐
if you paid us.
如果你付钱给我们。
- I would.
- Come, Patrick.
- 我会的。
- 来吧，帕特里克。
I'll make you
a free Krabby Patty
我会让你
免费蟹肉饼一份
for $2.50 plus tax.
2.50 美元（含税）。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
Well, you pulled it off,
Bubble Bass.
好吧，你成功了，
泡泡贝斯.
And you didn't even
have to flick a fin.
而你甚至没有
必须轻弹鳍。
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
- [growls]
Bubble Bass,
- [咆哮]
泡泡鲈鱼，
why do you think it's funny
to pack your mother in a box
你为什么觉得这很有趣
把你妈妈装进盒子里
and drag her all over town?
- Mother?
然后拖着她满城跑？
- 母亲？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- We'll just see
how you like it.
- 我们会看看
你有多喜欢它。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- I didn't do it!
Ow!
噢！
Mother, please--
[grunts]
妈妈，请——
[咕哝]
It was SpongeBob and Patrick!
[grunts]
这是海绵宝宝和帕特里克！
[咕哝]
I'll dry the dishes, Mommy.
[grunts]
我会把碗擦干的，妈妈。
[咕哝]
I love you, Mommy.
我爱你，妈妈。
[light twangy music]
[轻快的鼻音音乐]
♪ ♪